# SUDIP MAHARJAN

Designer

Ravi Bhawan Kathmandu

110

+977 9865072119

mahsudip10@gmail.com

@mah\_sudip 🔘

## **ABOUT ME**

A highly motivated and hardworking individual, to finish job accurately. I believe in quality over quantity. Well-organized and precise with excellent multi-tasking skill. Ability to develop design deliverables - mockups, and front-end development. Experienced with Adobe Creative Suite, particularly with After Effects and Premier Pro, and has a knowledge of 'Motion Design.'

# **EDUCATION**

(2016 - 2020) KATHMANDU UNIVERSITY

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science

(2014 - 2016) GEMS INSITUTE OF HIGHER EDUCATION

HSEB Board, Science Major

#### **EXPERIENCES**

(2020 - Present) MOTION DESIGNER, Spiralogics Inc.

Created and executed graphics in After Effects and Illustrator. Utilized various computer software and programs to create designs and videos.
Manipulated visual images to convey motion. Animated characters using plugins to place cartoons into motion.

(2020 - Present) VIDEO EDITOR, Spiralogics Inc.

Recorded and edited many video projects for instructional videos,
Animated videos, Explainer videos and infographics. Guided video content
and production processes to achieve ultimate results.

(2020 - Present) UI/UX DESIGNER, Spiralogics Inc.

– Created and executed UI mockups and prototypes that clearly illustrate how sites function and look like. Worked on Mockup creation (Figma) and web development (HTML, CSS & JS).

(Aug 2020 - Nov 2020) DESIGN INTERN, Spiralogics Inc.

– Designed and worked on UI developed for web/mobile. Engaged in website design, logo and icons designs.

#### (2019 - Present) FREELANCER

– Worked as a freelancer for outside projects. Created logo designs and animation, 2D animation explaner video.

### **SKILLS**

ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS	
ADOBE PREMIER PRO	-
ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR	
FIGMA	
ADOBE XD	
ADOBE PHOTOSHOP	
PROCREATE	-
HTML & CSS	-
JS (JAVA SCRIPT)	
GIT	